That has
happened
Om Om
[Music]
Call the
phone number Friends, you are very
welcome to my channel, I am
helping you Satan Qatil. In today's video,
we will talk about LIC's financial scheme
which will help you financially
or apart from this, even in your absence,
how will this file slide take care of your family.
Let's start
today's video. Do you have
a small child in your house, how much do you spend on that child?
Look people, you spend 5 to 10 thousand
rupees on a child till the age of five, then
how much money will you give to the child after the age of one? Perhaps
you should not ask even ₹1 from them
because in the coming time, they will be out of their own house and
perhaps the child will
not be able to fulfill their needs, but you do not
worry, we have such a child for you
whom you can raise and leave with me
for your upbringing and you can deposit ₹5000 every
month in it for its upbringing and I
guarantee you that when that child grows up, he will give
you 25000 rupees every month.  Urine test
tube of not only 25000, if God forbid
something happens to you, then this child will
give 25000 to your wife every month. Now tell me if your
children can do this, if not then would you
like to adopt such a child who will keep you and
your family safe and
also guarantee your retirement. Friends, it
is very important to have this function in everyone's house which will give you pension even in retirement
and if something happens to you then
give pension to your family. Have
you thought about this? If you have not thought about it then think and
see, this tea will always do good to you,
add it as soon as possible,
friends
why, for what purpose will it play for you regarding financial tea.
If you
like this video then please subscribe to my channel,
please like my video
and press the bell icon so that you
get the latest updates, with regard to which you get a
time for watching our video.